# **Denise Rocio Sosa**

## Full Stack Developer 🖵

**→**□ +542995520389

▶ Argentina, Neuquén

™ rocio.sosa94@gmail.com

Linkedin 🖴 | GITHUB

**Full-Stack Developer** with background experience in tourism management, hospitality, sales restaurant reception, tourist information and administration. These roles led me to become in a keen listener and empathetic person always trying to understand the specific needs of each client in order to provide them with the best digital solution.

Regarding the IT world, I've gained experience with GIT, data structures, object-oriented programming, algorithms, agile methodologies and eCommerce projects.

I have experience in both Front End and Back End development, using JavaScript, Node JS, React, Redux, Express, Sequelize, postgreSQL, HTML and CSS. I'm also learning Typescript and Tailwind.

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:**

### Full Stack Web Developer - Final project NGO Vamos!!

Jan. 2024- Feb 2024

Trainee in NGO VAMOS!! (Peru). Henry Bootcamp.

**Vamos!!**: We designed a web app for Vamos!! which is a NGO that offers transfer from different airports to specific destinations in Peru as well as empowering senior citizens with employment opportunities. It features user profile for trip bookings, and an administrative dashboard to organize bookings, drivers list, downloading reports, statistics and product prices.

**Frontend:** React, Redux. **Backend:** Express, Node JS. **DB:** PostgreSQL y Sequelize.

Frameworks: GIT, Chakra UI, Firebase, Cloudinary.

GitHub Vamos!! 🚓

## Full Stack Web Developer – Individual project: Dogs

Nov. 2023- Dec 2023

Academic project. Henry Bootcamp.

**Dogs:** A Single Page Application (SPA) designed to showcase different breeds of dogs while allowing users to create and store new breeds in the database. Besides, users are able to search by name, apply alphabetical sorting, sort by weight and filter breeds by temperament or origin.

Technologies:

Frontend: React, Redux, HTML and CSS.

**Backend:** Express, Node JS. **DB:** PostgreSQL and Sequelize. **Tools:** GIT, Thunder Client.

GitHub Dogs 😵

Academic project. Henry Bootcamp.

**Rick & Morty:** A Single Page Application (SPA) created to showcase the characters from the cartoon Rick & Morty. Users can log in using their email and password, select favorite characters, search by ID, alphabetically sort by name, and filter by gender.

## Technologies:

Frontend: React, Vite, Redux, Tailwind.

**Backend:** Express, Node JS. **DB:** PostgreSQL y Sequelize. **Tools:** GIT, Thunder Client, Testing.

## **OTHER EXPERIENCES:**

May 2022-May 2023

Receptionist • Hotel Casino Maverick • Plaza Huincul, Argentina.

Jul 2021 – Apr 2022

Receptionist •Hotel Antu Malal • Plaza Huincul, Argentina.

Nov 2021- Jan 2022

Administrative • Accountant Pablo Cerda • Plaza Huincul, Argentina.

Dec 2019 - 2021

Sales • Turisur SRL • San Carlos de Bariloche, Argentina.

Sep 2018 - Nov 2019

Sales and administration • Huilliches EVT • San Carlos de Bariloche, Argentina.

Jan 2018 – Mar 2018

Tourist information • Tourism Secretary • Dina Huapi, Argentina.

### **EDUCATION:**

- UX/UI program in Fundacion YPF and Media Chicas
- Full Stack Developer. Henry Bootcamp more than 800 hours theory and practice course 2023/2024.
- Tourism Management National University of R\u00edo Negro. Graduated year 2018. Argentina

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Redux & Redux Toolkit
- Typescript
- Tailwind CSS
- Figma

- Node.JS
- Sequelize
- PostgreSQL
- Express
- Agile Learning
- Firebase
- Chakra UI
- Cloudinary